Hello and welcome to another jumpsuit up video. Since we've only had like black or
black and white jumpsuits so far I thought let's bring in some color. So I
brought my badinka jumpsuits. I have three of them and I'm going to show them to you.
If you're a fan of just black jumpsuits, sorry, this is what's going to happen today
Although I'm telling you these are super cool. So stay tuned. I'm going to change into the first one
So that was so easy to get into them because they're super stretchy and super comfortable.
Badinka is a label from Hungary and these designs are amongst their famous ones because
they make a lot of this biomechanic sidewalk stuff and I think it's really cool.
Just look at that blue here.
So cool.
But I'm going to get some shoes now.
So I combined this suit with my Pleaser PVC boots.
I think they work great together, I don't know.
And what's also great with this suit is the face mask.
I did some pictures with a mask from Fnidmuskel
and it worked pretty well together although yeah at the moment it's a bit
too cold to go outside with this suit because it's not very thick but even
more stretchy. Although I like this one really much I'm going to change into the
second one it's going to be this one so let's go
I love this design but let's put on some shoes. This is like my favorite design ever I don't know why.
I think it's super creepy with the eyes and I love the color. Of course this would be great
for Halloween as well as the other one and a lot of people wear them for festivals because
they're comfortable and I've worn this... did I wear it at a festival? Not yet I think because
all the festivals have been cancelled. My plan was to get up in the morning put this on and sit down
in our camp because it looks so funny. Oh and by the way if you guys don't like these kind of shoes
we girls are going to wear them anyway because they're super comfortable. If you're at a festival
or a concept the whole day then you don't want to walk around in these high heels I
showed before with the other outfit but with like chunky platform boots because they're
so much more comfortable.
Get used to it.
I love that there is a hood and the design in the inside of the hood is the green version.
This looks so great together and I have a face mask from Badinka with the same
pattern in green. It looks great together. I think this looks so cool together. Fun
story, Badinka did a lockdown photo contest last year in April and the topic
was Quarantine. People should do pictures in their home like what they do in
Quarantine wearing the Badinka jumpsuits and I won first place with my... I think
it's a super cool picture with this jumpsuit and me chilling in the hallway
but yeah that was fun to make. And now on to the last jumpsuit. It's a completely
different one because it's golden and there are no arms. Badinka does not have
this jumpsuit anymore in their shop. I don't know why. I think it's really atypical for them.
But let's get dressed. Okay so this one is pretty different from the other two but I really like it
as well. I think it's awesome. It's so elegant somehow but with the hood it's also really
stylish and cool. I feel like I should be a part of Pimp My Ride or Crips or something with this outfit.
So which one was your favorite? Leave a comment below and tell me about it. I don't know,
I still think this one is my favorite because it was the first design I picked from Boudin
Cabou because I thought it's so cool. But I think the pleaser shoes work perfectly together with the
suit it's a clash of elements but it's golden hey and I also like the cool back
but enough now this was this video I hope you had fun please consider
subscribing to my channel and turn on the notifications have a nice day bye